[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "In applying an ACL to a router interface, which traffic is designated as outbound?",
    "choices": [
      "traffic that is coming from the source IP address into the router",
      "traffic that is going from the destination IP address into the router",
      "traffic that is leaving the router and going toward the destination host",
      "traffic for which the router can find no routing table entry"
    ],
    "answer": 2,
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "category": "Access Control Lists Quiz (14)"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What is the quickest way to remove a single ACE from a named ACL?",
    "choices": [
      "Use the no access-list command to remove the entire ACL, then recreate it without the ACE.",
      "Copy the ACL into a text editor, remove the ACE, then copy the ACL back into the router.",
      "Use the no keyword and the sequence number of the ACE to be removed.",
      "Create a new ACL with a different number and apply the new ACL to the router interface."
    ],
    "answer": 2,
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "category": "Access Control Lists Quiz (14)"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Which ICMP message type should be stopped inbound?",
    "choices": [
      "echo-reply",
      "echo",
      "source quench",
      "unreachable"
    ],
    "answer": 1,
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "category": "Access Control Lists Quiz (14)"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "Which scenario would cause an ACL misconfiguration and deny all traffic?",
    "choices": [
      "Apply a standard ACL using the ip access-group out command.",
      "Apply an ACL that has all deny ACE statements.",
      "Apply a standard ACL in the inbound direction.",
      "Apply a named ACL to a VTY line."
    ],
    "answer": 1,
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "category": "Access Control Lists Quiz (14)"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "Refer to the exhibit. A network administrator is configuring an IPv6 ACL to allow hosts on the 2001:DB8:CAFE:10::/64 network to access remote web servers, except for PC1. However, a user on PC1 can successfully access the web server PC2. Why is this possible?",
    "choices": [
      "The IPv6 ACL Deny_WEB is spelled incorrectly when applied to the interface.",
      "The IPv6 ACL Deny_WEB is applied to the wrong interface of router R1.",
      "The IPv6 ACL Deny_WEB is permitting all web traffic before the specific host is blocked.",
      "The IPv6 ACL Deny_WEB is applied in the incorrect direction on router R1."
    ],
    "answer": 2,
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "category": "Access Control Lists Quiz (14)"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "Refer to the exhibit. A network administrator wants to create a standard ACL to prevent Network 1 traffic from being transmitted to the Research and Development network. On which router interface and in which direction should the standard ACL be applied?",
    "choices": [
      "R1 Gi0/0 outbound",
      "R2 S0/0/0 inbound",
      "R1 S0/0/0 outbound",
      "R2 Gi0/0 outbound",
      "R2 Gi0/0 inbound",
      "R1 Gi0/0 inbound"
    ],
    "answer": 3,
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "category": "Access Control Lists Quiz (14)"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "Which two statements describe appropriate general guidelines for configuring and applying ACLs? (Choose two.)",
    "choices": [
      "Standard ACLS are placed closest to the source, whereas extended ACLS are placed closest to the destination.",
      "If an ACL contains no permit statements, all traffic is denied by default.",
      "The most specific ACL statements should be entered first because of the top-down sequential nature of ACLs.",
      "If a single ACL is to be applied to multiple interfaces, it must be configured with a unique number for each interface.",
      "Multiple ACLS per protocol and per direction can be applied to an interface."
    ],
    "answer": [1, 2],
    "type": "multiple-choice-v2",
    "category": "Access Control Lists Quiz (14)"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "Refer to the exhibit. Which statement describes the function of the ACEs?",
    "choices": [
      "These ACEs automatically appear at the end of every IPv6 ACL to allow IPv6 routing to occur.",
      "These ACEs must be manually added to the end of every IPv6 ACL to allow IPv6 routing to occur.",
      "These are optional ACEs that can be added to the end of an IPv6 ACL to allow ICMP messages that are defined in object groups named nd-na and nd-ns.",
      "These ACEs allow for IPv6 neighbor discovery traffic."
    ],
    "answer": 3,
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "category": "Access Control Lists Quiz (14)"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "What wild card mask will match networks 172.16.0.0 through 172.19.0.0?",
    "choices": [
      "0.0.3.255",
      "0.252.255.255",
      "0.3.255.255",
      "0.0.255.255"
    ],
    "answer": 2,
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "category": "Access Control Lists Quiz (14)"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "What method is used to apply an IPv6 ACL to a router interface?",
    "choices": [
      "the use of the access-class command",
      "the use of the ipv6 traffic-filter command",
      "the use of the ip access-group command",
      "the use of the ipv6 access-list command"
    ],
    "answer": 1,
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "category": "Access Control Lists Quiz (14)"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "What type of ACL offers greater flexibility and control over network access?",
    "choices": [
      "named standard",
      "numbered standard",
      "flexible",
      "extended"
    ],
    "answer": 3,
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "category": "Access Control Lists Quiz (14)"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "Which operator is used in an ACL statement to match packets of a specific application?",
    "choices": [
      "established",
      "gt",
      "lt",
      "eq"
    ],
    "answer": 3,
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "category": "Access Control Lists Quiz (14)"
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "Which two keywords can be used in an access control list to replace a wildcard mask or address and wildcard mask pair? (Choose two.)",
    "choices": [
      "some",
      "any",
      "gt",
      "most",
      "all",
      "host"
    ],
    "answer": [1, 5],
    "type": "multiple-choice-v2",
    "category": "Access Control Lists Quiz (14)"
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "Consider the following access list.\n\naccess-list 100 permit ip host 192.168.10.1 any\naccess-list 100 deny icmp 192.168.10.0 0.0.0.255 any echo\naccess-list 100 permit ip any any\nWhich two actions are taken if the access list is placed inbound on a router Gigabit Ethernet port that has the IP address 192.168.10.254 assigned? (Choose two.)",
    "choices": [
      "Only the network device assigned the IP address 192.168.10.1 is allowed to access the router.",
      "Devices on the 192.168.10.0/24 network are allowed to reply to any ping requests.",
      "A Telnet or SSH session is allowed from any device on the 192.168.10.0 into the router with this access list assigned.",
      "Devices on the 192.168.10.0/24 network can sucessfully ping devices on the 192.168.11.0 network.",
      "Only Layer 3 connections are allowed to be made from the router to any other network device."
    ],
    "answer": [1, 2],
    "type": "multiple-choice-v2",
    "category": "Access Control Lists Quiz (14)"
  }
]
